https://www.yorapper.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for www.yorapper.com
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [email protected]
At www.yorapper.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.yorapper.com and how it is used.
Log Files Like many other Web sites, www.yorapper.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons www.yorapper.com does not use cookies.
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Kontera.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.yorapper.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.yorapper.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.yorapper.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our site at www.YORAPPER.com(“Web Site”). Your privacy is important to us and we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit at this site. This policy applies only to YORAPPER treatment of personally identifiable information collected through our Web Site. YORAPPER has the right to share your information with third parties.
If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, please be advised that because we operate internationally, and certain of our computer systems are currently based in the United States, your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. By using the Web Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country, and you also consent to YORAPPER using your personal information to contact you electronically, in writing, or otherwise to provide notices relating to your use of the Web Site and to give you information about the products and services offered by YORAPPER and its affiliates. YORAPPER may store your information beyond this date if that is required by law or contract.
Information Collection and Use of Collected Information
Web Site Visitors
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 2000 or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).
Web Site Customers
In order to purchase products or services from YORAPPER, we require that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at this site include: name, address, e-mail address, mobile phone number and MSISDN (mobile station integrated services digital network number), credit card and billing information, download history, customer generated content and/or information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.
We may use such personally identifiable information to provide the information or content you have requested (e.g., fulfill your orders for our ringtones, data and news), to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested (such as future promotional materials), or for other purposes disclosed from time to time. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our Web Site or changes to our privacy notice, Terms of Service, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Web Site. In addition, we may use information collected about our users to improve the content and navigation of our Web Site, or for other internal purposes.
We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect from you with outside records (e.g., information we obtain from other companies, including wireless providers) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
To fulfill your requests for products and services (e.g., provide you with content via your mobile phone), we may share the personally identifiable information you provide with your mobile phone service provider or their partner and subcontractor companies. Our privacy policy does not cover such entities use of information. To learn more about your provider’s privacy practices, you should consult its privacy policy. From time to time, we may share personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties to enable them to provide you with opportunities to learn of products or services in which you may be interested.
We may also disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our Web Site or purchased a particular type of product.
In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information collected about you at this site in the following instances:
Legal Action: We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, when requested by governmental or quasi-governmental authorities conducting an investigation, hearing or the like, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.
Corporate Change: We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other corporate change respecting the Web Site.
Your Choices
As noted above, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect from you online to provide you with opportunities to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of such e-mail communications. You may not opt out of service-related notifications.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
Some of our Web pages contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors and Customers should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our site, we may use “cookies” on our Web Site. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we turansfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Web Site. However, once you become a Customer and furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you when you return to our site). You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web Site. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our site can be accessed only in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content.
Data Security
We have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security. Due to the open nature of Internet communications, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and YORAPPER will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Visitors of the Website and Customers use the site at their own risk.
Changes to Privacy Policy
We may, from time to time, update this privacy notice and such changes shall be effectively immediately and without further notice to you.
Questions/Concerns?
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please fill our contact form.
Effective Date
This notice was updated on or about July 2008
Recent Posts
Why Are The Yeezys So Popular?
Where to Buy Hip Hop Jewelry Online?
© 2020 YoRapper.Inc All Rights Reserved.
